~ Credits ~
Translator: Nigel
Editing: Skythewood
Timing: Mr. Shy
Alright, everyone! Just a little more until we’re done!
Let’s get fired up and go!
O-onee-chan, what’s that?
Oh! Mare, what’s the matter?
I heard a surprising sound, and I was curious about it.
Onee-chan, why did you summon so many Dragon-kin?
Hehe, what do you think?
What’s that... from the outside, it looks like Nazarick from the outside...
Exactly! I’m making another Great Underground Tomb of Nazarick!
Ueehhhh—?!
And it’s not just the outside which looks similar either! Even the interior’s almost the same!
How about that? Awesome, right?
...Hang on, why’re you looking so scared?
C-could it be...
O-onee-chan, you...
What?
N-nothing...
What are you trying to hide?!
Spit it out! Why you little~
I, I get it! O-onee-chan, are you planning to secede from Nazarick?
Haaaaaaah?! What are you talking about?! As if I’d do that!
B-But isn’t the point of building such a huge base to...
You... The reason I’m building this is because...
Ah, this presence is...
Gate, close.
Ainz-sama!
Things seem to be proceeding well, Aura.
Ainz-sama! You came!
Oh? You’ve made such progress in such a short time.
You have my thanks, Aura.
Ehehehe... th-there’s no need to thank me. It’s only natural that I should obey your instructions, Ainz-sama.
Ah... So does that mean making this other Nazarick was your idea, Ainz-sama?
Indeed.
We do not know when an external invader might come,
but in order to prepare for such a situation, we need to build a decoy to draw away said enemies.
This is also part of the plan to strengthen Nazarick.
I see...
Hm? What’s the matter?
Ah, no, I just thought onee-chan was going to go independent.
Eh? Independent?
Like I was saying, I wasn’t going to do anything of the sort!
I’m sorry, Onee-chan...
Jeez! Ainz-sama, please don’t get the wrong idea!
Oh...
Aura, on her own?! But how... Ah, but then there was Shalltear’s example from earlier.
Uhh...
Aura.
What is it, Ainz-sama?
Is there anything about your daily life which makes you unhappy?
Eh? Me?
Mm. I know you work very hard for me every day.
However, I have not repaid you in any way.
I was thinking if there was anything I could do for you.
What are you saying, Ainz-sama?
All this talk about repayment and... so on...
Exactly! There is no greater joy for us than to serve you, Ainz-sama.
I am very pleased by your answer, but this is a heartfelt wish of mine.
Ainz-sama, your...?
Rewarding subordinates who have discharged their duties diligently is the responsibility of their superior.
At the same time, it is also a source of joy.
That being the case, is there anything you want, Aura?
Well, this is all rather sudden...
There is no need to stand on ceremony, given the efforts you have made in building the fake Nazarick.
Ainz-sama, I’m very glad to hear that from you, but I can’t accept this by myself.
Is that so?
That’s because the other Guardians do work for you too, Ainz-sama.
It would be strange if I was the only one who received a reward.
That, that’s right, if Albedo-san or Shalltear-san learned that onee-chan was the only one who got a reward, then...
Indeed... that would be very bad.
I understand. Then, I shall bring this matter up at our next meeting.
I think that’d be a great idea, Ainz-sama!
Then, farewell.
Ah... Aura.
What is it?
I’ll be counting on you from now on.
Yes!
Then, that’s all we have for today. Is there anything else?
There is something I wish to discuss. Is that fine with you, Albedo?
Ainz-sama! Of course, please tell us whatever you wish.
Firstly, I would like to thank everyone for coming here today.
I wish to express my sincere gratitude to all of you for your daily efforts.
Ainz-sama! Those words of yours fill us with awe and delight!
However, for us, service to you is...
Albedo! I’m not done talking yet.
Forgive me.
Looks like you failed at scoring points.
Ara, and may I know what you meant by that, Shalltear?
Sucking up too hard has the opposite effect, you know.
Sucking up?!
I was merely expressing my sincere
feelings as Ainz-sama’s loyal minion!
A loyal minion, huh...
So is taking a hug pillow that looks just like your master to your bed
and drooling all over it something that a loyal minion should be doing?
Shalltear, how dare you make me lose face in front of a Supreme Being.
Are you prepared for the consequences of your actions?
Ara ara~ Your face is covered in wrinkles~
It must be tough being a virgin succubus like yourself~
That’s it! Let’s go, right now!
Contain. Yourselves. We. Are. In. The. Presence. Of. A. Supreme. Being.
My deepest apologies!
I’m very sorry!
Honestly. The. Two. Of. You. Are. Beyond. Hope.
This is standard fare for them, but really, they ought to have learned better by now.
Then, Ainz-sama, may I trouble you to continue speaking?
In truth, I have been thinking of instituting a fringe benefits system for Nazarick in order to reward everyone’s hard work.
Fringe... benefits?
What are those?
In my original world, there were institutions called “companies”.
Well, you can think of them as guilds.
Explaining in detail would take too long, but in short,
these “companies” provided free services known as fringe benefits to ensure their members could work comfortably.
That said, there were a lot of companies which didn’t provide those.
As a peon, I hardly benefited from them either.
Free services... is that it?
Indeed. For starters, I wish to construct the facilities that we will need in Nazarick.
I would like to improve the livability of Nazarick and the relationships between us.
Do any of you have any specific requests?
Ainz-sama, your suggestion is a marvellously tempting one,
but is Nazarick not amply furnished with all the facilities we need?
There is the Spa Resort Nazarick and the bar on the 9th Floor.
And the Manicure Salon too. Thanks to it, my nails are always in beautiful condition.
There. Are. Also. Snowy. Peaks. And. Dense. Jungles.
It. Would. Be. Easier. To Name. Something. Which. Was. Not. Present.
Is that so.
Ah... well...
Oh? That’s rare of your Mare, speaking up on your own.
I’ve been thinking about something ever since I heard you speak some time back, Ainz-sama...
There’s no need to hold yourself back.
Nazarick belongs to you as well.
I will grant any wishes you have.
Then, I want the sea!
The sea, you say?
Yes! I could grow more plants and raise more animals if there were a sea in the 6th Floor’s jungle!
I say, there should be a limit to what you’re asking for!
So, so I can’t? As I thought...
No, let’s listen to the others first.
Is there anybody else?
Speaking of which, if I had to ask for something, I would have to request a torture room.
Is. There. Not. Already. A. Torture. Room. On. The. 5th. Floor?
I would like a little more variety in the torments which could be inflicted.
Burning, drowning, crushing with stones, and then the administration of drugs.
Something like the Sanzu river might add flavor to it as well.
Is, is that so...
Onee-chan, is there anything you need?
Me? Well, if I could pick, I’d want a taming room!
A place where I could whip to my heart’s content!
Is. That. Not. The. Same. As. The. Torture. Room?
Taming is nothing like torture! You can’t tame without love!
Aura, torture does not work without love either.
Really?
Ainz-sama! May I be permitted to speak?
Er... um... I guess...
If it pleases you, may we have a children’s room?
With pink walls, a mobile hanging from the ceiling, and a crib in the middle with a baby in it...
Why would you need something like that?!
That’s none of your business, Shalltear.
I have no objections with building that room, but I have opinions of my own on the design.
The walls should be black, the hanging toys should be bats, and the crib should be a rocking cradle.
Why are you butting in?!
Isn’t that obvious? I’ll be the one using that room in the end.
Shalltear. It seems we will need to settle this with a duel.
Ara, but why do we need to do so when the outcome is so plainly obvious?
Indeed. Settling matters aside, I’m the one who will bear the Supreme One’s child...
Come, Ainz-sama! Let’s discuss the room’s decor!
Get away from Ainz-sama, you vixen!
Silence!
My deepest apologies!
I’m very sorry!
It feels like I’m experiencing deja vu...
We’ll leave that matter for next time. Dismissed!
Ainz-sama, may I know where you are going?
I have personal matters to attend to.
The word “benefits” sounds so simple, but everybody wants different things.
Providing everyone with the fringe benefits they want ought to offset the chances of betrayal.
Of course, I’m not doubting everyone’s loyalty,
and in Shalltear’s case, it’s not entirely out of the question.
If there’s something I can do about it, I should first...
Ainz-sama.
Demiurge, is it?
By coming to the 1st Floor, did you intend to head out?
No, I didn’t...
There is no need for you to tell me.
I am fully aware of your plans, Ainz-sama.
You must have wished to see if we could protect you under any circumstances, am I correct?
Mm, indeed, that is the case.
Please be at ease, Ainz-sama.
My subordinate demons lie in waiting, ready to deal with any eventuality.
Is that so? Thank you for your hard work.
I have also surmised your intentions from your wise proposal just now, Ainz-sama.
By “proposal”, do you mean the matter of fringe benefits?
Indeed, I do. As expected of you, Ainz-sama.
Drawing out potential traitors by such means is the height of excellence!
Traitors?
Those who are easily tempted by benefits can be easily bought.
By laying bait before everyone, you can clearly gauge their reactions.
It is a most effective way of assessing their loyalty.
Indeed, that was what it was...
I didn’t plan on doing that in the first place...
Oh well, forget it.
Anyone who was visibly tempted by such an offer would be worth watching from now on.
However, Ainz-sama...
What is it?
In truth, I trembled in fearful awe when you bellowed just now.
We could not possibly betray one who possesses such a regal bearing.
I can vouch for that.
Dignity, huh...
I’m returning to my room. Please maintain your vigilance.
Certainly.
Ainz-sama doesn’t seem to have come back yet.
Then, do excuse me. Here I come~
It doesn’t matter when— Ainz-sama’s scent is the most fragrant of them all!
I’d best breathe in as much as possible while I can.
Footsteps? Has Ainz-sama returned already?!
I think I’ll lie down for a bit...
The sheets feel warm... Why is that?
That was close. Fortunately I managed to dive under the bed.
Well, this is a situation which makes my heart beat faster too~
Dignity... It’s quite important.
Ainz-sama’s talking to himself! This is a rare opportunity to hear what he truly thinks!
Nobody will follow the man who stands at the head of an organization if he doesn’t have charisma.
That said, being able to maintain the appropriate dignity at all times is difficult to say.
I must act in a dignified manner at all times.
Ainz-sama seems troubled.
As the Guardian Overseer, I must
listen to everything he says!
How should I maintain my dignity, though?
Would acting be enough?
If I’d known, I would have trained up some acting-type skills.
Still, I don’t know if they’d be of use in this world.
To think it was... acting?
Ainz-sama seeks acting ability?
Better acting would also make life easier during my activities as an adventurer.
Still, there’s no point talking about it at this point.
Now then, I ought to be heading back to work.
I’m probably imagining things.
It is a vassal’s duty to offer what her liege desires.
Ainz-sama scolded me twice today.
The plan was to use Albedo as a stepping stone to get near him...
But it’s not working out...
Ara? This sound...
It sounds like it’s coming from the Great Library of Ashurbanipal...
Is that... a pile of books?
Seems to be moving...
There’s wings coming through the gaps in the books...
Now, who has wings as as special feature... Albedo?
Is Albedo in that pile of books?
Still, what’s she doing there...
It’s not this one, or that one... It should be around here...
That’s it! Found it!
As long as I have this, Ainz-sama will...
Well, that’s the picture of suspiciousness...
Although it’s rare enough that’s she’s not suspicious.
Still, I wonder what she has in mind for Ainz-sama...
Ainz-sama~!
Albedo, what’s the matter? You seem flustered.
My deepest apologies for forcing you to witness this wretched state of mine.
May I trouble you for a moment of your time?
It’s fine. Go ahead.
A few days ago, you mentioned something about, ah, fringe...
Fringe benefits?
Well, on that note, how about building a theatre in Nazarick?
A theatre, you say?
I feel many of Nazarick’s residents seek entertainment, so there will be demand for it.
That may be so.
Empires of old often used entertainment to dispel their citizens’ unhappiness and ward against the threat of betrayal.
Since we will be conquering the world in future, it might be worth your consideration.
I see. While I find this a very interesting proposal,
remodelling Nazarick ought to wait until I’ve gotten everyone’s opinions first.
Please do not worry about that.
I have obtained the signatures of most of the Floor Guardians, including that of Demiurge.
To think she had moved so fast...
I see. I admire your passion, but what about the performances?
You’d need a script, wouldn’t you?
Of course! I’ve prepared one already!
This script... did you take it from the Great Library of Ashurbanipal?
Indeed, I did. This script seems to have been brought over from the world you used to reside in, Ainz-sama.
That must have been Tabula Smaragdina-san’s doing.
He was always a detail maniac.
That place collected great works of literature from all over the world,
be it Norse mythology, the Cthulhu Mythos or even the Tale of the Heike.
So, what’s it about?
Well, about that...
Why are you hesitating?
Didn’t you come here after verifying the contents?
Of course, I did.
This work is called “Romeo and Juliet”.
It is what is known as a “tragedy”.
A tragedy, huh... That’s not likely to win over the audience, is it?
According to Chief Librarian Titus,
this particular piece combines cultural significance and entertainment value,
and is very suitable for performances.
Well, alright, then. How about the actors?
Here it comes!
I am currently picking candidates from among the people of Nazarick.
The most important criteria is whether the choices suit the role.
After all, a fool cannot hide his true nature even if he plays a sage.
That really hurt for some reason.
Well, that does make sense, in a way.
First, we must select the person who will play the main character, Romeo.
Since Romeo is the eldest son of a noble family, I wish to have someone highborn take that part.
Then, who will it be?
That is obvious enough.
The highest-placed and most noble person of Nazarick can be none other than yourself, Ainz-sama!
Wait, that means...
I wish to make you the star of the show, Ainz-sama!
Oi, oi, what are you saying all of a sudden?!
Albedo, I do not have that much free time.
I cannot possibly accept such a request—
But this might be a good chance to practice your acting skills!
Say what?
What better way is there to improve acting skills than by a live performance as an actor?
That might be true...
I’ve never acted before!
Should I take part to gain a bit of experience?
No, but I don’t want my subordinates to see my awful technique...
Ainz-sama, does this unsettle you?
That, that’s because it was too sudden.
Please do not worry.
I will rehearse with you until you’re thoroughly satisfied with your acting prowess.
If it displeases you, you may drop out at any time.
I see.
Of course, the rehearsals will not be public. I will not permit anyone unrelated to come close!
Well, if that’s how it is, mhm—
I don’t see why I can’t give it a try.
Is that true?
Just as planned!
Then, let us not delay, here is the schedule...
Hold it right there!
Shalltear! We’re discussing very important busin—
I’ve already seen through your schemes.
Just give up.
Scheme?
What are you saying?
Could you please not try to quarrel with me right now?
If you insist on being difficult, I’ll tell all, right here and now.
What’s all this about, Shalltear?
I asked Chief Librarian Titus about Romeo and Juliet.
The story’s protagonist Romeo falls madly in love with the heroine Juliet—
But the two of them are torn apart by their families.
What a tragic development!
The problem is the last scene.
After Romeo collapses from drinking poison,
Juliet ki-ki-kisses... Gh!
After drinking Romeo’s poison, Juliet decides to end her life as well.
Not only it is tragic, but artistic!
What’s wrong with that?
Can you say that after seeing this?
That’s the cast list! Shalltear, where did you get that...!
I hope you haven’t forgotten that Nazarick’s maids don’t answer to you alone.
Shalltear, what is...
This is the cast list Albedo made.
To think, Albedo would actually write her own name beside Juliet’s!
What?!
Ainz-sama, if you were to play Romeo, then Albedo would end up kissing you!
She’s already the Guardian Overseer,
but she’s still plotting to steal your... your lips, Ainz-sama!
This is a terrible abuse of her power!
I see. So that was Albedo’s aim...
Even though I don’t have lips.
I had no impure thoughts in mind!
All I wanted was to help the play succeed!
If that’s the case, then why wasn’t I informed about it, hm?
That, that’s because...
Because you knew that your plans would be ruined if I found out,
so you decided to steal a march on me and get Ainz-sama’s approval, am I wrong?
Your mind’s moving pretty fast for a change, Shalltear.
However, even if that is true, so what?
Ainz-sama has already approved this project.
You wouldn’t want to stop the project halfway, would you?
Oh, I won’t say that.
Eh?
I will let it go forward. I simply wish for the cast to be picked fairly.
Fairly?
That is to say, by conducting an audition.
Demiurge?! What are you doing here—
Because Shalltear discussed it with me.
Then the reason you approved of my suggestion just now was because—
I approved of the script, but I do not recall approving of the cast list.
I trust nobody in Nazarick will object to Ainz-sama playing the star’s role.
However, the female lead is a different matter entirely.
If Albedo plays the female lead,
I can imagine many people,
Shalltear included, would be very unhappy with that decision.
In order to avoid that, I feel the female lead’s role should should be decided in a fair manner.
Hence the auditions, then?
Indeed. I doubt anyone will complain if you show your prowess with a fair and open audition.
Kuh, but—
Ara, Albedo. Afraid of losing?
What are you saying, Shalltear?
I won’t lose to the likes of you.
Then, if you’re so confident, you don’t have any reason to refuse the audition, do you?
I understand.
Then, I shall clearly illustrate the difference between our respective abilities in a public forum.
Prepare yourself, Shalltear!
Fine by me.
Ainz-sama, forgive me for approaching you out of turn,
but would you be willing to give your permission for for the audition?
I have the feeling this is going to cause a lot of trouble.
Still, it’s not like an armed showdown.
Being able to settle this peacefully should be pretty good, no?
I understand. Then, I will leave the oversight of the matter in your hands, Demiurge.
I thank you for your kind words.
Since the name of Nazarick depends upon it, I shall hold a firm but fair audition.
What’s going on?
Why are there so many people around?
Look, Onee-chan! There’s a notice board over there.
A notice board? Let's see...
“Audition Brief: Let’s Choose Nazarick’s Female Lead!”.
What’s this about?
I guess it’s to determine who’ll be the female lead of Albedo-san’s play.
It says participants have to play
out the events of the final scene.
Ah~ so that’s it.
What’s this, what’s this?
Anyone interested may fill in their names.
Hmmm— anyone can take part, then.
Onee-chan, aren’t you taking part?
Hah? Me? I’m not that kind of girl.
Besides, look.
The field for the names of the participants.
After Albedo wrote her name in such big letters, Shalltear went and signed her name in bright red ink.
That’s a declaration of war.
I’ll pass on fighting with those two.
Well, you say it’s a fight,
but there won’t be any actual fighting, right? So you don’t have to hold yourself back...
You don’t know anything, do you?
Ah, you look so cute, but you’re just a boy, Mare.
Eh, w-what does that mean, what happened?
Women will do anything to win when they get serious.
Especially those two.
Is that so...
I think the others would agree with me.
Ah?
While they say the audition results will be decided by voting, I’ll bet most of them will abstain.
But that means it won’t be a fair trial, then?
That’s true, but what do you think will happen if word gets out that you voted for one of them?
Who knows what kind of revenge the other side will take.
I don’t think even those two would lay a hand on people from Nazarick...
Under normal circumstances, that would be true.
But this time, it concerns their feminine pride.
Who knows what will happen?
You seem different from how you normally are...
Ma~re~ what did you mean by that?
A-Ahh... I didn’t mean anything special...
Honestly. It. Has. Become. Quite. A. Mess.
Cocytus. Well, I guess you're right.
To. Think. He. Would. Approve.Of. Such, A Farce... Has. Demiurge. Gone. Mad?
Wait! Do you mean Demiurge organized all of this?
That’s. What. I’ve. Heard.
I don’t think Demiurge would have gone to all that effort without any other intentions...
He must have something up his sleeve.
Hmm~ So that’s it.
What happened, onee-chan?
Well, this might look quite interesting, hee hee...
So there’s three days until the auditions...
All I wanted was to practice my acting,
but I have no idea how I ended up becoming part of an event which involved all of Nazarick.
Why is it that things get so out of control around Albedo and Shalltear?
Those two are... how shall I put it, so extreme.
Well, I suppose that’s a charm point for them.
That is...
Why, why hast thou abandoned me?
Why hast thou abandoned me?
Cast me aside and departed by thyself.
Drunk all, and left no friendly drop to help me after?
...Hap’ly some poison yet doth hang on thy lips.
She looks really serious. This is the first time I’ve seen Albedo with that look on her face.
Ainz-sama!
Forgive me, I had no intention to eavesdrop.
No, it is my utmost regret to have failed to notice your mighty presence, Ainz-sama. Please accept my sincerest apologies.
Pay it no heed. Still, does that not indicate how focused you were on your practice? You looked like you were about to complete a passionate performance.
No, I... I am not satisfied with my technique yet.
Is that so...
Indeed. In truth, I even sought out Pandora’s Actor’s suggestions.
Him?!
What did he say?
“The most important skill one can have for acting is love! Liebe! Fall in love, young lady!” and so on.
That guy!
Although, I decided to act on his advice in my own way...
The less of his advice you listen to, the better.
Yes.
Then, I shall look forward to the rehearsal.
Ainz-sama!
What’s the matter? You sound so serious.
While this request might be untoward in the extreme...
May I trouble you to help me practice?
My sincerest apologies for my rude request!
N... No...
If this inspires her, why not give it a try?
Well, if it’s just for a while, it should be fine.
Really? Ah~ how wonderful! To think you would personally help me practice, Ainz-sama...
Mm, hm. Then, what should I do?
Ah, I hope you could just lie down over there.
You just need me to lie down?
Yes. In the final scene, Romeo has perished after drinking poison, so all you need to do is lie down there.
Eh? Is that it?
Is that alright?
Then, please allow me.
Why hast thou abandoned me?
Cast me aside and departed by thyself?
Drunk all, and left no friendly drop to help me after?...
It feels like she’s getting really close.
And her breathing’s getting really fast...
Hap’ly some poison yet doth hang on thy lips...
To think I’d get a chance like this before we officially go on stage?
I, I can’t stop myself any longer!
This, this is bad!
If this keeps up, she’ll take my first kiss! Is it really alright to lose it like this?
She’s breathing so hard that it’s ruined the romantic mood...
No, not that it would be fine if the mood was romantic in the first place!
Albedo!!
Shalltear! That’s—!
It’s a Purifying Javelin!
Get away from the Supreme Being now! Or else...!
Walls of Jericho.
You think that feeble defensive wall of yours can block the Purifying Javelin?
My skill build is specialized for defense.
Blocking that pathetic lance of yours is child’s play.
Then try it!
Bring it on!
Stop that right now!
To think the two of you would use your skills in Nazarick, and on your fellow comrades!
What is wrong with you?!
My sincerest apologies!
I’m very sorry...
I’m tired of hearing you apologize!
Cool your heads, both of you!
Ah... Ainz-sama!
I was scolded by Ainz-sama again...
And whose fault do you think it was?!
That’s really sneaky of you, Albedo.
I... I was just having Ainz-sama help me rehearse.
I can see that lewd look in your eyes and that wicked expression plastered all over your face.
I came because I could hear you panting like a dog from so far away.
Eh? Is, is that so?
Well, if you’re willing to abandon your image for that, then I won’t hold back either.
And what is that supposed to mean?
I will use any means to claim the Supreme Being’s lips.
Wait, Shalltear!
Good luck.
What does Shalltear have in mind...
The audition is tomorrow, and while Shalltear doesn’t seem to have done anything so far,
I don’t think matters will end just like that...
Ara, isn’t that Aura?
So... so the audition’s tomorrow! Good luck!
Th-thank you.
Then, bye!
She seemed very strange...
Could you hang on a little?
Ah... W... What’s this about, Albedo? You look really scary.
Have you seen Shalltear recently?
Hah?! Of course not!
Really?
Why are you lying? It’s not like you at all.
That’s because...
Could it be that Shalltear asked you to do something?
Eh?! How did you know?
So she did, then?
What did she ask you?
She wanted me... to vote for her...
As I thought!
And how did you answer her?
“You’re really making things difficult for me, even if you ask like that!” or something.
I see...
So Shalltear was trying to form a voting bloc...
Who else did she approach, besides you?
Hm... I wonder. I’m not too clear on the details myself.
I don’t think she spoke to anyone besides the Floor Guardians.
Ara? Why is that?
That’s because the others don’t want to get involved with something annoying like this.
The Pleiades have all washed their hands of this.
Anyone who’s not on your or Shalltear’s level might end up losing their lives if anything happens.
Then, I’ll go find the other Floor Guardians and ask them.
Ah... that sounds great! Seeya!
Aura, I’m not finished yet.
What is it?
Could you vote for me?
Like I said, I don’t want to be bothered by requests like that!
How about we make a deal, then?
Ah... that, that’s!
Kal Kan, a legendary item said to be able to lure out the magical beast that stands above all other creatures.
I’m sure it must be very attractive to anyone who collects animals.
Are, are you tempting me with this?
Shalltear’s forming a voting bloc, so I need to respond by any means necessary.
Mm~ But~
Consider this a deposit.
Once I get your vote, I’ll give you the superior item known as Kal Kan High Grade.
Uuu, that’s unfair!
It doesn’t matter how you see it.
I’d rather become a devil than let
Shalltear take Ainz-sama’s lips!
Training as always.
I’d expect nothing less of Cocytus the warrior.
Shalltear.
Why. Have. You. Come. All. This. Way?
It’s about tomorrow’s audition...
I. Refuse!
But I haven’t said anything yet.
There. Can. Be. Only. One. Reason. For. You. To. Approach. Me. On. The. Day. Before. The. Auditions.
My, aren’t we sensitive.
Of course, I don’t expect you to help me for nothing.
Bribery. Is. A. Stain. On. The. Proud. Name. Of. Nazarick!
As expected of Cocytus, he reacted exactly as I thought he would.
Could you remove your weapon?
I didn’t come here to bribe you.
Then. Why. Are. You. Here.
Cocytus, do you wish to cross blades with Ainz-sama?
You. What. Are. You. Saying—
Warriors wish to battle the strong, do they not?
You wish to battle Ainz-sama from the depths of your heart, and it is not an impossible thing.
However, as a Floor Guardian, baring steel at Ainz-sama is forbidden.
Then, what about a battle on
the stage, what do you think?
On. Stage. You. Say?
There is a character known as Tybalt, who fights a duel with the main character Romeo.
Even if it’s only a fictional setting, you will be doing battle with Ainz-sama.
Tempting, isn’t it?
What. Are. You. Saying?!
Your blade is trembling.
At least your body is honest.
Begone! I. Will. Not. Succumb. To. Your. Temptations!
If. You. Count. Yourself. As. A. Member. Of. Nazarick. Then. Dispense. With. These. Tricks. And. Fight. Me. Fair. And.Square!
I understand.
I knew it would not be easy, but he refused me in the end.
I didn’t manage to win Aura over either. If this keeps up...
Thank you for coming, everyone.
We shall begin “The Grand Grand Grand Audition For Nazarick’s Female Lead” shortly!
Demiurge is really getting into it.
He. Is. Hosting. The. Event. So. He. Wants. To. Stir. Up. The. Crowd.
Really...?
May the best woman win, Shalltear.
When did you make that outfit?
Sewing is a lady’s hobby, you know.
Looks aren’t everything, you know!
Then, may I trouble you for the
opening speech, Ainz-sama?
First, I’d like to thank the two of you for your hard practice until today.
I want you to settle things today, with a clean, honest battle of acting ability.
Understood?
Yes!
As for the rest of you... well, the fact is that you’ve all forfeited.
I hope you will judge their acting with impartial eyes.
That’s all.
Thank you for blessing us with those wonderful words.
Then, let us begin the audition!
For this audition, we shall have our contestants act out the final scene of Romeo and Juliet.
As Romeo is dead, I have prepared
a dummy as a substitute.
That— that’s Albedo’s hug pillow!
I specially lent it out.
Looks like Ainz-sama, don’t you think?
You did wash it, didn’t you?
Of course.
Then, ladies, you may begin when ready. How do you wish to do this?
Shalltear, after you.
Albedo actually gave way to me.
Does she have something in mind?
Even so, I can’t back down here.
Then, I shall gratefully accept and begin.
First up— Shalltear!
Then, begin!
Calm down! I have to be calm!
I need to make Ainz-sama
notice my good points!
Shalltear’s crying!
A. Rare. Sight.
Romeo-sama!
Whyfore hath thou abandon’d me and depart’d by thyself?
Shoulds’t thou not hath left some sweet nepenthe for me?
What a thrilling performance.
Ainz-sama’s noticing me!
I’ve got a good feeling about this!
Mayhaps thine lips bear a trace of thy fell concoction.
With but a kiss...
There’s something moist on the dummy’s lips!
Is this... poison?!
Did you really have to apply real poison to it?!
Albedo, you...!
Huh? She’s stopped.
How. Strange.
I need to calm down!
Even if I point it out now, there’s no way I can link this poison to Albedo.
And besides, poison has no effect on the undead like myself!
That being the case...
She’s kissing it!
Kids shouldn’t be seeing this!
But why?
How shall I say this...
I didn’t expect Shalltear to have such a mature expression on her face.
Romeo-sama!
Thus do I hasten to your side!
She stabbed herself with a knife!
She. Deliberately. Suppressed. Her. Regeneration. To. Allow. The Blood. To. Flow.
What. Admirable. Determination.
Thank you for watching, everyone.
Shalltear, are you alright?
They say you need a sense of realism for acting skills.
Let it bleed for a while.
Is that so...
And that was Shalltear’s performance.
Next, we shall have Albedo demonstrate her thespian abilities.
It’s my turn.
What a shame, Albedo.
Your plot failed.
Whatever are you talking about?
You can pretend all you want, but the snare you’ve set has caught you instead.
And what does that mean?
I kissed the dummy, but the poison is still on it.
Now that you’re in costume, you’ve also removed your poison immunity gear.
I doubt you’ll be able to kiss the dummy now.
Is that so...
She seems so relaxed... what’s that about?
Does she have some kind of plan to deal with it?
Then...
Begin!
Romeo-sama...
Why did’st thou abandon me, to depart by thyself...
At the very least, thou should’st have left the sweet venom for me...
She’s really calm, unlike Shalltear-san.
Is. That. The. Mindset. Of. Those. Who. Face. Death?
I. Can. Sense. The. Devotion. Hidden. Within.
Perhaps some trace of venom remains upon these lips...
But with a kiss...
Doesn’t look like she had a spell cast on her.
Albedo shouldn't be able to kiss it like that.
What does she intend to do?
My beloved Romeo-sama...
Spare some poison for me...
Albedo! What is she thinking?!
Is it me or does Albedo look like she’s in pain?
That dummy’s been smeared with poison!
If we don’t stop her now—!
Hold!
But why, Cocytus-san?
Look. At. Albedo’s. Face.
She. Seeks. Desperately. To. Suck. The. Poison. From. Her. Lover’s. Lips.
Is. That. Not. To. Be. Expected?
But if this goes on, Albedo-san will...
What amazing spirit.
Ainz-sama...
She continues expressing her love despite going through such suffering.
Is that not how Juliet should look?
Could that have been Albedo's aim from the beginning?
She poisoned the dummy to show Ainz-sama her realistic acting skills!
Did she even factor in my poison immunity?!
Romeo-sama...
I’m heading to your side... right now...
Demiurge-san!!
That’s enough!
Cure Poison!
Ainz-sama...
Shalltear, you come here too.
Yes...
I’ll heal you as well.
Thank you very much, Ainz-sama!
The two of you went way too overboard.
Still, that was an exciting performance.
Your words fill me with gratitude.
It’s too early to relax just yet.
Indeed, the judging begins now.
Then, let us begin the voting now.
Circle the name on your votes and then hand them to me.
Also, as the host of this event, I shall abstain from voting for fairness’ sake.
Also, I hope you will watch in silence, Ainz-sama.
After all, your opinion overrules everyone else’s.
W... What should I do...
I. Have. Already. Decided.
Me too.
I’ve done everything I can.
Victory is mine!
It’s not over yet!
Then, I shall declare the votes.
One vote for Shalltear.
One vote for Albedo.
They are tied.
Therefore, it is a draw!
How could this!
Those are the results.
This is strange!
Why are there only two votes?!
Who abstained!
T... That’s because... I couldn’t decide...
That means Aura and Cocytus voted.
Aura should have voted for me.
You voted for Shalltear, didn’t you, Cocytus?
No. I. Was. Moved. By. Your. Resolve. Albedo. So. I. Voted. For. You.
Eh? But that means...
Sorry.
Aura! How could that be!
After I promised her the Kal Kan High Grade, the deal should have been sealed!
Could it be that she betrayed me?
I was hesitating until the end~
That item in Aura’s pocket is...
Kal Kan Premium!
That divine item before which even divine beasts must kneel!
It’s so hard to obtain, but who...!
Shalltear!
How dare you give her something better than the item I promised her!
Since it’s a draw, does that mean
we should have a do-over?
How could you do such a shameless thing?!
Ara, what are you talking about?
You bribed Aura, didn’t you?!
Would you mind not trying to pick a fight?
You call this picking a fight?!
Aura, show me that item!
You gave this to Aura, didn’t you?
Do you have proof of that?
We’ll know once we ask Aura. Isn’t that so?
Did Shalltear seal her lips?
Doesn’t sound like proof to me.
What happened, Aura?
Please answer!
Albedo and Shalltear both gave me items.
Hang on. Aura, what are you talking about?
I have proof.
The Eyeball Corpse witnessed the deal.
Shall we call it over?
What’s this? It’s as though she knew we were going to make a deal!
Ah, could it be...
My, my, what’s all this about?
They both tried to bribe me.
Is that so. Well, we can’t have that.
According to the rules, any misconduct is grounds for disqualification.
Demiurge, was this part of your plan?
Oh, what are you implying?
You used Aura to make us both cheat, and thus disqualify us both!
Was that what it was?!
It distresses me when you say so without any proof.
All I did was make thorough preparations to ensure a fair audition.
I simply told the Guardians to inform me if either of you approached them.
Were we dancing in your hands all along?
If either of you won, it would leave behind the seeds of resentment.
Therefore, the sole conclusion was to have the two of you lose.
Thus was my strategy decided from the beginning.
Your strategy was on a different level, Demiurge.
This. Is. The. Retribution. For. Being. Tempted. By. Desire. And. Resorting. To. Foolish. Trickery.
There is no need for either of you to be unhappy.
Ainz-sama!
How can we apologize for showing this pathetic side of ourselves to you?
It is a shame that all these events have occurred.
However, I feel I have gained greatly by watching the two of you act.
Both of you have worked hard, haven’t you?
Ainz-sama!
Thank you very much for your benevolence!
No matter who wins, it might sow the seeds of future conflict...
Indeed, Demiurge was right.
This is a pretty good ending to
the matter, all things considered.
Then, everyone, let’s—
E... Er, would you permit me to delay you a little?
Mare~ What's wrong with that?!
I, I’d like to join the auditions too.
Hah?!
Now?
There was no closing date on the sign-ups, and it wasn’t stated that males weren’t allowed...
I... Indeed, that is true...
Mare, you’re kidding, right?
Are you aiming for Ainz-sama’s lips too?
It’s not like that.
But after I saw the two of you perform, I wanted to try too...
Can I? Ainz-sama?
Why is Mare so suited to skirts!
Don’t look at me from that cute angle!
Demiurge. It. Seems. You. Have. Lost.
T... Then, we shall continue the auditions...
Wait! Hold it right there! I won’t hand over Ainz-sama’s lips!
Mare, tell me what you want, okay?
You! Are you trying to bribe people again?!
I just wanted to stand on stage...!
Ma-Mare!
They still ended up fighting in the end...
Silence, all of you!