Credits ~ Translation: SifaV6, Skythewood, Rockgollem
~ Editing: TaintedDreams, Ferro, Rockgollem, JcqC ~ Timing/Encoding: JcqC
Haaa...
Ara, Narberal, you sound tired.
Of course, Yuri-nee sama.
Momon-sa... No, I received orders from Ainz-sama, so I can’t relax.
That, I know.
With Ainz-sama.
It's happy, but scary.
That's right, Shizu.
But for Ainz-sama's orders,
I will carry out with all my heart and...
We will end the chit chat there.
We will now start the monthly Pleiades report and the tea party.
Yuri-nee sama~ Is Lupu absent today~?
Entoma, you already know Lupusregina is busy over at the human village.
That kind of question is unnecessary.
Ara~ Solution, we need to confirm for sure~
This is an important monthly meeting after all~
That's enough both of you.
Entoma, prepare the tea and the snacks.
Yes~
I, no, I, the Deputy Leader,
Yuri Alpha will now open this session.
In this session, there are 3 things to report.
From me and... Narberal?
Yes, on my side, we traveled with 2 humans after receiving a request through the Adventurers' Guild from some human noble.
We vanquished Gigant Basilisk along the way. With Ainz-sama, of course.
Together with Ainz-sama?
What? Kuuu— I'm so jealous—
Narberal is being cocky.
You should have seen Ainz-sama when he took down Gigant Basilisk...
Narberal, that's enough.
For my report, it was with Shizu.
We held The 1st Great Tomb of Nazarick Love Love Ainz-sama Guardians’ Special Grand Auction.
Yes, we hosted the auction.
But... that terrible name...
It sounds like she came up with the name...
She’s not a bad person, but...
Narberal, and now Yuri-nee sama...
And Shizu as well~
To receive orders in name of Ainz-sama...
I'm so jealous~
Ah! Solution~ Give that arm to me~
There are a lot of right-handed humans, right~?
That means~ There's a lot of men with tasty right arm~
The blood splattered.
It went in my drink.
Aaah... Sorry~
You drink it as punishment.
Ara, how many thousands of calories are in one cup?
I don't know for sure, but there's enough for an active adult to have nothing else for the entire day.
Drink.
Eh heh heh... Yuri-nee sama...
Entoma, it's no good to waste food.
Ugghh... It's tasty but...
Then third report is from Solution.
You were gathering information in the Kingdom with Sebas-sama, correct?
Yes, there are no problems and the plan is progressing smoothly.
But most certainly, tender meats from young girls are the best.
Especially when it's alive.
Hehe, considering how Solution eats~
Does the quality of the meat really matter~?
You seem to have finished drinking it.
It should taste like chocolate, banana and strawberry.
I like the sensation of eating them alive.
Since Ainz-sama didn't allow for it, be content with the men we finished interrogating.
But can't we ask him if we can eat one of them while they're still alive?
Agreed~
I'll think about it.